Guide to the Leslie Cagan Papers TAM.138
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Subject Files Accessioned 1993-2014
  - MFS: 8th National Conference: New York, NY, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - MFS: 9th National Conference: Washington, DC, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - MFS: 20th Anniversary "March for Jobs and Freedom": Washington, DC, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - MFS: Administration, 1981-1984, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - MFS: Affiliated Organizations, information from, 1982-1983, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - MFS: Anniversary of Hiroshima and Nagasaki Bombings, 1982-1985 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - MFS: Anti-Draft, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - MFS: Anti-Intervention Task Force, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - MFS: Boston, MA, 1983, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - MFS: Campaign for Peace with Justice in Central America, 1981-1983 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - MFS: Central America Peace Alternative: Organizer's Packet, 1983-1984, undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - MFS: Coordinating Committee, 1980-1984 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - MFS: Correspondence: Memoranda, 1981-1983 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - MFS: Correspondence: Memoranda, 1984, undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - MFS: Correspondence: Memoranda: Midwest Field Office, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - MFS: Disarmament Action Day: June 20, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - MFS: Disarmament: Nuclear Freeze Campaign, 1981-1983, undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - MFS: First Strike and EuroMissile Campaign, 1983-1984, undated (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - MFS: First Strike and EuroMissile Campaign: October Actions to Stop EuroMissiles, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - MFS: Flyers, Literature, undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - MFS: Interim Committee, 1981-1984 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - MFS: Jobs with Peace: Human Needs, 1981-1983, undated (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - MFS: Mailings: Outreach to Affiliates 1, 1980-1983 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - MFS: Mailings: Outreach to Affiliates 2, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - MFS: Middle East Peace Campaign, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - MFS: "The Mobilizer", 1982-984, undated (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - MFS: Multi-Cultural Tour, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - MFS: National Survival Education Fund, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - MFS: Proposals: Working Papers, 1981-1983, undated (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - MFS: "Peace not war in '84": Nationwide Petitions, 1983-1984, undated (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - MFS: Religious Task Force, 1981-1983 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - MFS: Reproductive Rights, 1981-1982 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - MFS: Staff/ Facilitator Meetings: Agendas and Minutes, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - MFS: Staff Meetings: Agendas and Minutes, 1982-1984 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - MFS: Staff Review: Correspondence and Memoranda, 1980-1981, undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - MFS: Staff Review: Meetings and Reports, 1980-1984, undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - MFS: UNSSDII, 1981-1982, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - NCIPA, 1984-1989, undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - NCIPA: Alternative Budget, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - NCIPA: Flyers, Literature, 1984-1989, undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - NCIPA: Mailings and Outreach, 1983-1989, undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - NCIPA: Press Clippings, 1986-1988 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - NCIPA: Rainbow Coalition, 1984, undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - NCPME: Administrative Committee and Staff, 1991, undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - NCPME: Advertisements, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - NCPME: Affiliated Organizations, 1990-1991, undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - NCPME: Affiliated Organizations, African American, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - NCPME: Affiliated Organizations, Literature, 1990-1991, undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - NCPME: Affiliated Organizations, Religious, 1990-1991, undated (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - NCPME: Affiliated Organizations, Student, 1990-1991, undated (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - NCPME: Budget and Finances, 1991, undated (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - NCPME: Cartoons and Graphics, 1990-1991, undated (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - NCPME: "Citizens Call to Congress", 1990, undated (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - NCPME: Coalition to Stop US Intervention in the Middle East, New York, NY, 1990-1991, undated (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - NCPME: Correspondence, Faxes 1, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - NCPME: Correspondence, Faxes 2, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - NCPME: February 23rd Meeting Registration, undated (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - NCPME: Flyers, 1990-1991, undated (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - NCPME: Gulf Crisis TV Project, The, New York, NY, 1991, undated (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - NCPME: Humanitarian Aid, 1991, undated (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - NCPME: Legislature and Lobby Day, 1990-1991, undated (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - NCPME: Mailing List, 1990-1991, undated (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - NCPME: Mailing List, Organization Directory, 1991, undated (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - NCPME: Mailings, Outreach, 1990-1991, undated (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - NCPME: Meetings, 1990-1991, undated (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - NCPME: National Coalition of Conscience, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - NCPME: National Day of Protests, April 6th, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - NCPME: Organization Directory, Response Forms, undated (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - NCPME: Peacenet Event Listing, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - NCPME: Political Papers, Statements 1, 1990, undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - NCPME: Political Papers, Statements 2, 1991, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - NCPME: Political Statement, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - NCPME: Press Clippings 1, 1990, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - NCPME: Press Clippings 2, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - NCPME: Press Releases, 1990-1991 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - NCPME: Project Proposals, 1991, undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - NCPME: Racism and Repression, 1990-1991, undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - NCPME: "Strategy 900" Letter Writing Campaign System, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - NCPME: Steering Committee, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - National Lawyers Guild: Amici Brief, Representative John Conyers, etal. Versus President Ronald Reagan, etal., 1984 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - National Lesbian Conference, Durham, NC, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - "New York State Campaign for the People's Budget" Conference, February 4, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - People's Alliance, 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Rainbow Coalition: By Laws, 1986-1989, undated (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Rainbow Coalition: Brochures, Literature, Pamphlets, 1988, undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Rainbow Coalition: Cagan, Leslie: notes, 1988, undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Rainbow Coalition: Conferences, Conventions, 1986-1990, undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Rainbow Coalition: Correspondence, 1988-1991 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Rainbow Coalition: DC Statehood, 1990. undated (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Rainbow Coalition: Journal Articles, Press Clippings, 1988-1989, nd. (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Rainbow Coalition: Labor, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Rainbow Coalition: Lesbian, Gay Commission, 1987-1989 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Rainbow Coalition: Letters to the Board, Memoranda, 1987-1991 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Rainbow Coalition: Mailings, 1986-1992 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Rainbow Coalition: National Board Meetings, 1987-1992 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Rainbow Coalition: New York State Chapter, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Rainbow Coalition: Position Papers, Reports, Speeches, Strategy, 1986-1990. undated (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Rainbow Coalition: Press Releases, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Rainbow Coalition: State Chapters, 1986-1991 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Rainbow Coalition: Structure Commission, 1989, undated (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Rainbow Coalition: Voter Registration, 1989, undated (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Rainbow Coalition: Women's Commission, 1986-1988 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Redwood Records Cultural and Educational Fund, 1985-1987 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Susan Saxe Defense Committee, undated (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - UNSSDII: Affiliated Events, International, 1982, undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - UNSSDII: Affiliated Events, United States, 1982, undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - UNSSDII: June 12th Rally Committee, 1982, undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - UNSSDII: June 12th Rally Committee: Correspondence, Mailings, Outreach, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - UNSSDII: June 12th Rally Committee: Flyers, Literature, 1982, undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - UNSSDII: June 12th Rally Committee: March and Rally Logistics: Buses, Housing, Police Routes, Transportation, 1982, undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - UNSSDII: June 12th Rally Committee: Press Release, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - UNSSDII: Non-Governmental Organization Liaison Group, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - UNSSDII: Press Clippings, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - UNSSDIII: National Coalition in Support of :Administrative Committee, 1988, undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - UNSSDIII: National Coalition in Support of :Banking, Petty Cash, Receipts, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - UNSSDIII: National Coalition in Support of: Bills, Outstanding Debt, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - UNSSDIII: National Coalition in Support of: Budget, Fundraising, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - UNSSDIII: National Coalition in Support of: "Call for Actions", Sponsors, Schedule of events, Mobilization Organization, 1988, undated (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - UNSSDIII: National Coalition in Support of :City Sound Productions Debt owed to, 1988-1990 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - UNSSDIII: National Coalition in Support of: Financial Follow-Up, Fundraising Letters 1, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - UNSSDIII: National Coalition in Support of: Financial Follow-Up, Fundraising Letters 2, 1988-1990 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - UNSSDIII: National Coalition in Support of: Flyers, Literature, 1988, undated (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - UNSSDIII: National Coalition in Support of: International Peace Conference, International, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - UNSSDIII: National Coalition in Support of :MFS Education Fund, IRS Documents, Non-Profit Status, 1984-1988 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - UNSSDIII: National Coalition in Support of: Outreach, Mailings, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - UNSSDIII: National Coalition in Support of: Press Release, Press Packet, Press Clippings, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - UNSSDIII: National Coalition in Support of: Program, speakers, 1987-1988 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - UNSSDIII: National Coalition in Support of: Steering Committee, 1988, undated (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - UNSSDIII: National Coalition in Support of: Peace Wave, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - UNSSDIII: National Coalition in Support of: Press Release and Report, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - MFS: Fortieth Anniversary of Hiroshima and Nagasaki: Tour and Booklet, 1985 (Box 16A, Folder 1)
  - Mobilization for Survival (MFS): Washington, D.C.: Follow-up, 1985 (Box 16A, Folder 2)
  - MFS: Affiliate List, 1985 (Box 16A, Folder 3)
  - MFS: Personnel Matters, 1985 (Box 16A, Folder 4)
  - MFS: Structural Items and Programs, 1985 (Box 16A, Folder 5)
  - MFS: Disarmament: General, 1983-1986 (Box 16A, Folder 6)
  - MFS: Nuclear Free Zone, 1982-1984 (Box 16A, Folder 7)
  - MFS: Weapons Facility Network, 1985 (Box 16A, Folder 8)
  - MFS: Deadly Connections: Other Groups, 1984 (Box 16A, Folder 9)
  - MFS: Deadly Connections: MFS Material, 1983-1984 (Box 16A, Folder 10)
  - MFS: Central America, 1983-1985 (Box 16A, Folder 11)
  - MFS: General (Leaflets, Mailings, The Mobilizer), 1984-1986 (Box 16A, Folder 12)
  - MFS: Domestic Issues, 1985-1986 (Box 16A, Folder 13)
  - MFS: Budgets, Debts, Events, 1981-1985 (Box 16A, Folder 14)
  - MFS: General (Leaflets, Mailings, The Mobilizer), 1986 (Box 16A, Folder 15)
  - MFS: Staff and Facilitators Meetings and Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 16A, Folder 16)
  - MFS: Staff and Coordinating Committee Meetings and Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 16A, Folder 17)
  - MFS: General, 1984-1985 (Box 16A, Folder 18)
  - MFS: Meeting with Third World Activists, 1983-1984 (Box 16A, Folder 19)
  - MFS: Nuclear Power, 1984 (Box 16A, Folder 20)
  - MFS: Correspondence: General, 1983-1984 (Box 16A, Folder 21)
  - MFS: Correspondence: General, 1985 (Box 16A, Folder 22)
  - MFS: Correspondence: General, 1985-1986 (Box 16A, Folder 23)
  - MFS: East-West Discussion in MFS, 1984 (Box 16A, Folder 24)
  - MFS: Lesbian/Gay Network, 1983-1985 (Box 16A, Folder 25)
  - MFS: Middle East: General, 1983-1985 (Box 16A, Folder 26)
  - MFS: Staff Evaluations, 1983-1984 (Box 16A, Folder 27)
  - MFS: Breaking the Silence Conference on the Middle East, 1985 (Box 16A, Folder 28)
  - Our Bodies, Ourselves (OBO): Correspondence, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - International Women's Year, undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - MFS: Survival Summer, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - MFS: Conference Program Proposal, undated (Box 17, Folder 3A)
  - Korea Solidarity Petition, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Puerto Rico, 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Chicago Women's Liberation Union, undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Boston Women's Union and Boston Area Socialist-Feminist Organization, 1973-1976 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Abortion Action Coalition Orientation Packet, undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - March 31, 1979: International Day of Action on Abortion (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Women's Movement Conference, Boston, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - International Women's Year: Lesbian and Left Presence and Information, [1977] (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - International Women's Year: Preparations, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Protest Against Reagan Presidency, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Susan Saxe Defense Committee, 1970s (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Mel King for Congress: General, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Mel King for Congress: Staff Meetings, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Mel King for Congress: Polls, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Mel King for Congress: Musicians and American Sign Language Interpreters, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Mel King for Congress: Petition Distribution and Return, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Mel King for Congress: Cagan's Memos to and from Key Staff, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Mel King for Congress: Media, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Mel King for Congress: Media Clippings and Letters-to-Editors, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Mel King for Congress: Press Releases, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Mel King for Congress: June 21 Office Party, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Mel King for Congress: Letter-Writing Campaign, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Mel King for Congress: House Parties, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Mel King for Congress: Get-Out-The-Vote, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Mel King for Congress: General, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Mel King for Congress: Fundraising Projects and Activities, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Mel King for Congress: Field: Voter Contact, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Mel King for Congress: Field: Top Priorities, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Mel King for Congress: Field: Meetings, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Mel King for Congress: Field: Memos and Correspondence, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Mel King for Congress: Field: Budget and Expenditures, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Mel King for Congress: General, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Mel King for Congress: Candidates' Forum on Central America, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Mel King for Congress: Canvass, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Mel King for Congress: Campaign Literature, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Mel King for Congress: Campaign Committee, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Rally for Peace and Freedom: March 18, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - NYU: Student Mobilization, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - NYU: Student Mobilization Committee Break-up, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - NYU: New Student Union, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Boston Area Socialist-Feminist Organization Pre-Conference, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Boston Area Socialist-Feminist Organization Conference: March 24, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Boston Area Socialist-Feminist Organization, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Boston Area Socialist-Feminist Organization, [1974] (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Boston Area Socialist-Feminist Organization, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Boston Area Socialist-Feminist Organization: Steering Committee Report, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 48A)
  - Boston Women's Union: Retreat, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Boston Women's Union: Steering Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Boston Area Socialist-Feminist Organization: Edelin Press Conference, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Boston Women's Union, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - International Boston Area Socialist-Feminist Organization Packet, 1974-1976 (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - Republican National Convention, Dallas, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - MFS: Survival Day/Survivalfest, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - National Network of Lesbian and Gay Male Socialists, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - Protest Against Reagan Presidency: Follow-up, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - Protest Against US Intervention in Central America and the Caribbean: June 7-9th, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - Northeast Coalition for Reproductive Rights, Boston, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - Boston Women's Union: Retreat, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 60)
  - NYU: Ad Hoc Committee for a Democratic University, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 61)
  - NYU: NYU Student Participation in October 21-22, 1967 anti-Vietnam War Demonstration in Washington, DC (includes non-print) (Box 17, Folder 62)
  - Democratic National Convention: San Francisco, California: Gay/Lesbian Left Information, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 63)
  - National March for Gay and Lesbian Rights: San Francisco, General, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 63A)
  - Mobilization for Survival (MFS): General, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - MFS: General, 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Abortion Action Coalition (AAC): Steering Committee: Correspondence, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Abortion Rights Action Week (ARAW), Oct 1979 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - ARAW, Sep 1979 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - ARAW, May-Jun 1979 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - March 31, 1979 Abortion Rights Demonstration: Local (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - March 31, 1979 Abortion Rights Demonstration: Regional and International (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - International Women's Day: Boston, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - ARAW: Boston, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - AAC: General, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Marxist-Feminist Conferences, 1976-1979 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - "Women in Vietnam" Conference, Montreal, Canada, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - January 24, 1981 Demonstration Against Reagan: "Inaugurating a People's Movement in the 1980s" (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - "Yes, We Can" Fair and Demonstration, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - National Socialist-Feminist Conference, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Susan Saxe Defense Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Susan Saxe Defense Committee: Susan Saxe Statements and Follow-up, 1976-1977 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Susan Saxe Defense Committee, Weather Underground, and Symbionese Liberation Army: Events and Communiqués, 1975-1977 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - New York University: Protest against Dow Chemical Corporation, 1967-1968 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - New York University: Ad Hoc Committee for a Democratic University, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - New York University: Racism and Martin Luther King, Jr. Memorial, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - New York University: Placement Office Incident, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - New York University: Student-Faculty Strike, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - New York University: Hatchett Affair, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - New York University: Solidarity with Columbia University Struggle, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Women's Coalition to Free Joan Bird (Panther 21 Case), New York City, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Red Tape Media Collective and The Women's Show, Boston, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Cambridge Committee on the Status of Women: Historical Committee, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Cambridge Committee on the Status of Women, 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Boston Area Socialist-Feminist Organization: Support for Dr. Kenneth Edelin, Undated (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Anti-Repression [i.e., FBI] Leaflets, Undated (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - International Women's Day Demonstration (March 19, 1983), Boston (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Boston ARAW: Mailing Lists and Mailings, 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - AAC and Abortion: General, Late 1970s (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Socialist-Feminist Group: Meeting Notes and Anti-Zionism Open Letter, 1976-1982 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Women's Expo Leaflet, Undated (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Women's Network (Ad Hoc Coalition of Boston Area Feminists/Boston Women's Coalition), 1981 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Socialist-Feminist Conference ("A Dialogue on the Women's Movement"), 1981 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Gay/Lesbian March on Washington, DC (October 14, 1979) (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Sterilization and Puerto Rican Women's Federation Tour, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Boston Gay Socialist Group, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Just Peace Project, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Reproductive Rights National Network: Petition for US Representative Henry Hyde, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Chicago Socialist-Feminist Abortion Meeting, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Berkeley-Oakland Women's Union (BOWU), 1975 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Boston Lesbians and Gay Men Against the Right: Campaign against Proposition 6 (Briggs Initiative) in California, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - [Unidentified Organizing Documents], [1970s] (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Lucy Parson's Women's Coalition (Boston), Undated (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Coalition for a Non-Nuclear World, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - National Gay Task Force, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Mobilization for Survival: Survival Education Fund: Legal, 1978-1981 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - MFS: To-Do Lists, 1982-1986 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - MFS: Fortieth Anniversary of Nuclear Bombing of Japan, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - MFS: Hiroshima-Nagasaki Days, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - MFS: Cruise-Pershing II Conference, Boston: Information Packet, Leslie Cagan talk, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - MFS: Boston: General, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - MFS: Boston: Coordinating Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - MFS: MFS Course, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - MFS: North Atlantic Network, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - MFS: Boston Harbor, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - MFS: NYC Harbor, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - MFS: Navyport Referendum Campaign, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - MFS: General, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - MFS: "Deadly Connections" Information Packet, 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - MFS: Educational/Organizers' Packet on "Amerika", 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - MFS: Children of War Tour, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - MFS: 10th Anniversary of MFS, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - MFS: South Africa, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - MFS: Organizational Task Force and Affiliates, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - MFS: National Conference, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - MFS: April to October, 1986 Actions (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - MFS: Affiliate Mailings, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - MFS: Publications: General, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - MFS: March 1986 Cape Canaveral Action, 1985-1987 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - MFS: Conference and Travel Reports, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - MFS: Central America, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - MFS: Coordinating Committee Meetings and Staff Mailings, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - MFS: Deadly Connections, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - MFS: Mobilizer, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - MFS: Middle East, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - MFS: Feminist Task Force, 1984-1987 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - MFS: Domestic Issues, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - MFS: Disarmament: General, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - MFS: Central America: November 12th Coalition, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - MFS: Central America: November 12th Coalition, 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - MFS: Central America: November 12th Coalition, 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - MFS: Central America: November 12th Coalition: Demonstration, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 38)